feralinteractive.com 2012-05-04

# Feral Interactive : Privacy Policy

| 

We are committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our Web site. This Privacy Policy explains the choices that you can make about the way your information is collected and used. It is available for you to review on our homepage and at least on every page where we have requested personally identifiable information, including from kids under 13 years old. By using this web site, you signify your assent to the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with any term in this Privacy Policy, do not use this Web site. 

### KIDS

Please check with your parents before entering any information on this or any other Web site. See our **"Special Note to Kids"** below. 

### PARENTS:

We are committed to protecting children's privacy. We developed this Web site to be an enjoyable experience for customers of all ages. We recognize that some younger children may not understand some of the information contained on this Web site or how this Web site operates. Please be sure to caution your child against providing personally identifiable information online prior to the web site operator obtaining your consent. It is our policy not to knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without a parent's or guardian's permission. See our **"Special Note to Parents of Kids Under 13"** below. 

Please discuss this Privacy Policy with your children so that they will better understand how to use this Web site and the information they may be asked to provide. We strongly believe that providing our visitors with accurate and adequate notice about the Web site will lead to informed choices and decisions about how to use the Web site, as well as protecting our users' privacy. 

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

Generally, we limit the collection of information to what is known as non-personally identifiable information (e.g., first name, age, state or country).  We also collect certain types of personal information such as an email address. This information is collected so that visitors can participate in activities, such as receiving our e-mail newsletter.

In some areas on our Web site additional personally identifiable information is asked for and collected (for example, full name, mailing address and phone number). This collection is necessary so that our visitors can participate in certain activities, such as online sweepstakes or online promotions. You may not be able to access those areas or participate in such activities without being registered or giving us the necessary personally identifiable information. Whenever we request that you submit such personally identifiable information, we will notify you of our intended use of the information, as more specifically discussed below. Please be aware that we are prohibited from conditioning a child’s participation in an activity on the child’s disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity. You are under no obligation to provide, and can decline to provide, any requested information at any time. However, if you decline to provide personal information that is reasonably necessary to participate in certain activities, you may not be able to participate in those activities at this web site.

The types of information collected at this Web site may include: 

  * Contact information, such as full name, e-mail address and mailing address. 
  * Financial information and/or Credit/Debit Card data (for, by way of example, online store purchase)
  * Demographic information, such as date of birth, age, aggregate information, gender, state and country.
  * Internet Protocol (IP) Information, such as your IP address and browser type. 

### HOW DO WE USE INFORMATION?:

**Registration:**

Our Web site's registration form requires users to give us contact information. All registration information is submitted to us on a voluntary basis. Once you register, we use customer contact information from the registration form to contact you, to send you information about our company and/or to give you updates on products and/or services. You may register on our Web site and choose not to receive information and updates by unchecking the relevant box on the registration form. Kids, get your parent's or guardian's consent before you register or provide any information.

**Product Support for Feral Interactive customers:**

To send an email to Feral Interactive Ltd's ("Feral") Technical Support team regarding a problem you encounter with a Feral product, we may ask you to provide your name, email address, and information about your computer in addition to information about the product you are having trouble with. The email you provide to Feral for this purpose is used only to respond to the sender’s problem.

**Online Promotions:**

We or our licensees and/or other business partners may have special online promotions which feature products or services related to our business activities. To participate in any promotion, you must be 13 years or older (unless otherwise specified by the promotion's rules and regulations). If you are under 13 you will need your parent's or guardian's consent before you can participate in this activity. If you are 13 or older but not an adult you will need your parent's or guardian's consent to collect your prize or receive your benefit. You may be asked to provide an e-mail address or screen name, so that we can let you know if you won a prize. For other promotions, we may request your name and home address in order to send you products or information by regular mail. The specific rules and regulations governing the particular promotion will vary and your participation constitutes your agreement to abide by those rules and regulations. 

**Collecting and Sharing Data:**

The following outlines the ways we share your information. We do not share your personally identifiable information in ways other than as described in this Privacy Policy. We sometimes collect information to find out how people found our Web site, which pages they visited, and how long they stayed. In addition, we may aggregate demographic and non-personal information you provide and use such aggregate information to better design our Web site and to improve our marketing strategy and our product offerings.

We also use third-party service providers to assist in our service offerings. Such providers may include a credit card processing company, an outside shipping agent to fulfill delivery of orders, and an email service provider to facilitate our e-mailings. We will share your personal information with these types of third parties to facilitate functions on our behalf, even if you are under age 13. We require these companies to limit their use of your personally identifiable information to the purpose of fulfilling their services to us.

In some instances, such as when making a purchase using MasterCard SecureCode or Verified by Visa, you may be directed to the service provider's Web site to conduct the transaction by entering in your personally identifiable information. Although these pages may have the look and feel of the Feral Web site, please be aware that you are actually submitting your information directly to that service provider to fulfill your request.

Other than as explained in this policy, we may disclose personal information (including the personal information of those under 13) in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to: comply with legal processes; respond to any claims; or, protect the rights, property or personal safety of Feral Interactive Ltd., its subsidiaries and affiliates, our customers or the public. In addition, information about our customers, including, without limitation personal information regarding customers under 13, may be disclosed as part of any bankruptcy, merger, sale, transfer of company assets or acquisition. In the instance of a bankruptcy, merger, sale or transfer of company assets we will attempt to notify you. Please see our **“CHANGES”** section below.

**Opinions:**

We may ask for your opinion from time to time. You may send us questions or comments, which may require personal information for a response. If you are under 13, you will need your parent's or guardian's consent before you can provide this information.

**Mailing lists:**

You always have the right to unsubscribe from any mailing lists we may maintain, or to delete personally identifiable electronic information we have collected online about you by clicking the 'unsubscribe' link found within the newsletter email. Alternatively, you can email us at the Contact Information below, and we will remove you from our databases. Parents, you can always ask us to review or delete any of your child's information and you can refuse to permit further collection and use of your child's information at any time by sending us a written request at the Contact Information below.

**E-mail and Newsletters:**

We may offer fully interactive registered email services. Our newsletters may include links to independently operated Web sites. Although we do not provide any personally identifiable information about kids under 13 to any "independently-operated Web site" (that is, a Web site not owned, controlled and operated by us), such Web Site(s) may solicit personally identifiable information from kids under 13. Please be aware that we don't control and are not responsible for their actions, privacy policy(ies) or terms of use. If you are under 13, you will need your parent's or guardian's consent before you can participate in these activities.

**Purchasing Items:**

Purchasing items from our online store may require the giving of personally identifiable information (such as, name, credit card information). Information collected in this manner will be used consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

**Information Collected by Cookies and other Automated Processes:**

We use "cookies" to collect non-personally identifiable information through this Web site. Cookies help us personalize your visit for example by allowing you to use certain features without having to remember passwords or by logging in each time you visit. 

**Cookies:**  
Cookies are files that web servers place on an Internet user's computer that are designed to store basic information (such as visitor preferences). The use of cookies allows visitors to enjoy more seamless visits and more accurately measures visitor behavior.

There are two types of cookies that may be used on our Web site: a persistent cookie and a session cookie.

**Persistent Cookies:** A persistent cookie gets entered by your web browser into the "Cookies" folder on your computer and remains in this "Cookies" folder after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to our Web Site.

**Session Cookies:** A session cookie is held temporarily in your computer's memory and disappears after you close your browser or shut off your computer.

**Web Beacons:**  
Our Web site may also use web beacons in conjunction with cookies. web beacons are small strings of code that are placed in a web page, (sometimes referred to as "1x1 clear pixel," "web beacon" or "clear GIF") in the pages of our Web site in order to gather additional statistical site usage information.

**Site and Usage Analytics. Our Use of Persistent Cookies, Session Cookies, web beacons, and related technologies.**

Our Web site may use persistent cookies, web beacons and information collected in our log files (such as Internet Protocol Address, referring URLs, etc.) about your activity at our Web site.

  * We use this collected information to better understand how our Web site is used, resolve technical problems, and enhance your experience at this site.
  * Information we may collect using these technologies may include: 
    * the number of visitors to the Feral Web site,
    * which pages are visited,
    * duration of page views,
    * advertising click-through metrics,
    * the location of visitors prior to accessing their Web site, and
    * details on browsers (including Internet Protocol 'IP' addresses or browser configurations).
  * We use this information to produce detailed reports and analyses of the traffic to our Web site.
  * Information from these types of cookies and technologies or about Web site usage is not combined with information from any other Web site cookie like those described below that may be used for online behavioral advertising purposes. Except with respect to our e-commerce activities (e.g., on-line purchases), we do not link your non-personally identifiable information in "cookies" with personally identifiable information about you.

**Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out:**

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us by clicking the 'unsubscribe' link found within the email. Alternatively, you can email us at the Contact Information below, and we will remove you from our databases.

**IP Address and Machine Type:**

An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from our Web site, our servers log your IP address. An IP address does not contain personally identifiable information. Except with respect to our e-commerce activities (e.g., on-line purchases), we do not link IP addresses with personally identifiable information. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. We may also collect information about your browser software and/or machine type (e.g., Windows, Mac, Unix, etc.). 

**Links:**

We do present links to the Web sites of other parties. If you are under 13, get your parent's or guardian's consent before linking to other web sites. Independently operated Web sites are not associated with or authorized by us, even if they have links leading to this Web site. We are not responsible for any content appearing on Web sites linked to or from our Web site, or for any personal information gathered at those independently operated Web sites. 

**International Visitors and Customers:**

This Web site is hosted in the EU. If you are visiting from other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from EU law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the EU, and in doing so you consent to:

  * the use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
  * the transfer of your personal data to the EU as indicated above.

**Data Integrity and Security:**

We take reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure. We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the confidentiality and integrity of the information we collect. The information is stored on computer servers which are separate from other corporate information and systems. We have and will continue to take reasonable measures to assure the security and accuracy of all information our visitors share with us. Our efforts include procedures designed to avoid any unauthorized access, alteration, misuse or disclosure of personally identifiable information. 

Our Web sites which collect sensitive financial information, such as credit/debit card information use (or our third-party service providers) SSL encryption in the collection and transfer of such information.

If we learn of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this Web site or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site. We may post a notice on our Web site if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the feralinteractive.com Web site. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using the Contact Information below to submit your request.

### CHANGES:

**Changes in this Privacy Policy:**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy here and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. For registered users, if we make material changes to how we use personally identifiable information we will attempt to notify you by email so that you may make a choice to how your information is used. For children who are registered users, if we desire to change our use of personally identifiable information collected from children under age 13, we will obtain parental consent prior to implementing such changes. If we do not receive such consent we will not use the child’s personally identifiably information in the new manner.

### SPECIAL NOTE TO KIDS:

If you are under 13 years old, ask your parent or guardian **before** giving out any information about yourself, such as your name, age, address or e-mail address. You do not have to give any personal information about yourself. Remember, if you are under 13 you must have your parent or guardian make any changes to information given to us in the past or to update your profile. If you are ever unsure about anything you are seeing on this Web site, ask your parent or guardian for help. If you are 13 years or older, you may have the ability to participate in online contests or sweepstakes on portions of this Web site, however you cannot collect any prizes without your parent's or guardian's consent. 

If you are under 13, we may knowingly collect your email address, which is personally identifiable information, with your parent’s permission. We currently use your email address information in order to send a newsletter to you as approved by your parent(s).

### SPECIAL NOTE TO PARENTS OF KIDS UNDER 13:

You can always ask us to review or delete any of your child's information and you can refuse to permit further collection or use of your child’s information at any time by sending us a written request at the Contact Information below. However, if you ask us to delete your child's information that is necessary to participate in our activities, we may have to ask your child not to participate in our activities. 

We do not currently collect, use or disclose personally identifiable information from kids we know to be under 13 absent parental consent.

**To What Web sites does this Privacy Policy Apply?**

The terms of this Privacy Policy apply to all information submitted on [feralinteractive.com](http://www.feralinteractive.com/) and not to information that may be submitted to us offline. It does not otherwise apply to any independently operated Web sites, for which separate privacy policies and terms of use shall apply.

### CONTACT INFORMATION:

We hope you have a better understanding of our commitment to protect privacy. If you have any questions or comments about anything in this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following address: 

If you wish to review, correct or delete information that Feral may have about you or your child, or wish to inform us that you do not permit further collection or use of your child’s information, please contact us at the following address: 

Feral Interactive  
64 Kimber Road  
London  
SW18 4PP  
Attn: Webmaster   

Thanks. Have fun!
